(Amy:)This is nice,
that we all get to eat together.
(Leonard:)Absolutely.
(Amy:)Can we maybe put the phones down and
have an actual human conversation?
(Sheldon:)We can, but thanks to Steve Jobs,
we don't have to.
(Penny:)Guys. Guys,
you're never gonna believe this.
(Leonard:)-What happened?
-I just got a part on a TV show!
-That's great!
-Congratulations!
-Guys!
-Oh, yeah!
-Yay, Penny!
-What's the show?
NCII, or, you know, NCSTD--
(Penny:)I don't know, it's...
It's the one with all the letters
and I'm gonna be on it!
-That's amazing!
-Yeah.
(Howard:)-What's your part?
-I play a customer in a diner
(Penny:)and I flirt with Mark Harmon.
(Raj:)Ooh, Mark Harmon,
he's a dreamboat.
-So it's just flirting?
-Well, yeah. Why?
(Leonard:)No reason. I just think it's sexier
(Leonard:)when things are left
to the imagination.
(Amy:)He's wrong.
I (THEME SONG) I